ルカ子よ
男だったのだ
落ち着いて聞いてくれ
実は お前は 本当は
Rukako...
はあ…
Please calm down and
listen to what I have to say.
また そんなこと言うんですか？
You used to be a man.
待て 泣くな
落ち着いて 最後まで聞いてくれ！
これも全て まゆりのため
お前には
男に戻ってもらわなければ
ならないんだ
You're saying this again?
Wait! Don't cry...
Just let me finish!
All of this is for Mayuri's sake.
I need you to go back to being a guy.
Fractal Androgynous
はあ…
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
焼きそばの湯切りに失敗して
You're making a face, like you screwed up
your yakisoba noodles,
麺を全部流し台に
ぶちまけたような顔をして
and tossed them all into the sink.
むしろ
I'd prefer you to say
必死でためたスタンプカードを
いざ使おうとしたら
I look like someone who tried to use
all their discount card stamps,
有効期限が
切れていたときのような顔と
but discovered the card had expired.
言ってくれ
ウフッ…
冗談で返せるくらいの余裕は
あるみたいね
I guess you aren't so depressed,
you can't make a joke.
オカリン！
Okarin! Mayushii is very disappointed in you!
まゆしぃは オカリンに
がっかりなのです
な 何の話だ？
Wh-What are you talking about?
しらばっくれてもダメなんだよ！
Don't try and fool me!
るかちゃん泣かせたでしょ？
な なぜそれを…
You made Ruka-chan cry, didn't you?
H-How did you know...
一緒にラボに行こうって誘ったら
急に泣きだしちゃったんだから
When I asked her to come to the lab,
she just started crying.
それで
｢どうしたの？｣って聞いたら
And when I asked her about it,
｢お前は男だ｣って言われたって！
she said you told her she's a guy!
あっ…
Ｄメールのことも聞いたのか？
You heard about the D-mail?
D-mail?
Ｄメール？ ごまかそうとしても
ダメなんだからね
I told you not to try and fool me!
オカリンは きちんと
るかちゃんに謝るべきなのです
You should apologize to her.
はああ…
岡部！
うん？
Okabe...
そんなひどいことを漆原さんに？
You said something that awful to Urushibara-san?
いや 待て！
違うんだ これには訳が…
Wait! It isn't what it seems.
There's a reason for it...
どんな訳だ！
ううっ…
I don't care-
助手よ 一緒に来てくれ！
はあ？
Come with me, assistant...
いいから！
うわ～っとと… ちょっと何よ！
Come on!
Wh-What is it?
という訳で
次に取り消すべきＤメールは
So the next D-mail I need to erase is the one
ルカ子が生まれる前
Rukako sent to her mother's pager,
before she was born.
自分の母親のポケベルに
送ったものだ
漆原さんが 実は男？
Urushibara-san actually was a guy?
信じられない…
I can't believe it.
だが事実だ
But it's true.
事実だった
It was true...
彼女が男…
She was a guy...
もしかして… 橋田みたいな？
Was she like Hashida?
えっ？
あっ…
これはひどい
Fail.
ではなくて 見た目は あのままだ
No! She looked just like she does now.
なら許す
Then it's okay.
とにかく まゆりを救うためには
ルカ子を男に戻さねばならない
Anyway, to save Mayuri,
I have to get Rukako back to being a guy.
だけど 今回 岡部は
But you already know
漆原さんが送った
Ｄメールの内容を
what the D-mail she sent said, right?
知ってるわけでしょ？
だったらわざわざ
事情を話さなくても
Then you don't have to tell her.
黙って
取り消せばいんじゃないの？
You could just do it yourself.
俺は ルカ子の母親の
ポケベル番号を知らないのだ
I don't know the number for her mom's pager.
それに 下手な小細工を労するより
And I thought it would be better for her
真実を告げた方が まだ誠意はある
if I told her the truth, instead of trying to lie.
その誠意を見せた結果
泣かせちゃったわけでしょ？
Your guess at what's better made her cry, right?
そんなの いつもの設定ですよね？
That's just your usual thing, right?
冗談… ですよね？
Some kind of joke...
うっ ひどいです
That's mean!
岡部さんから
そんなこと言われるなんて…
I never expected you would say that to me.
うっ うう…
ていうか それ
フラグが立ったんじゃない？
Isn't that a flag there?
フラグ？
俺は この戦いが終わったら
A flag?
I never said anything like,
結婚するなどとは
ひと言も言っていないぞ
"Once this battle is over, I'm getting married."
それは ｢死亡フラグ｣だ
That's a death flag!
I'm talking about a love flag.
私が言ってるのは ｢恋愛フラグ｣よ
恋愛？
Love?
そう 大好きな岡部から
Her beloved Okabe told her she's really a guy,
｢お前は男だ｣と言われて
乙女心がズタズタになったのよ
and it damaged her maiden's heart.
いいっ… いやっ
しかし ルカ子は男だぞ？
No... But Rukako is a guy.
それは前の世界線の話でしょ？
That was in the last world line, right?
うん？
あっ…
Sender: Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe-san,
I've something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
"I've something important to say..."
｢神社まで来てもらえませんか？｣
Would you come to the shrine?
ふふんっ！
あっ…
岡部さん
Okabe-san.
さっきは すまなかったな
I'm sorry about earlier.
いえ… 僕の方こそ
泣きだしたりして
No, I'm sorry for crying.
それで 大事な話というのは？
And?
What did you want to talk about?
はい あの 僕 お願いが…
Right. Well... I have a request.
｢お願い｣？
A request?
僕 岡部さんが言ったこと信じます
I believe what you told me.
それで あの…
And so, um...
うん？
男に戻る代わりに
I'll become a guy again, but in exchange...
こっ こい…
P-Please...
Be my boyfriend!
恋人になってください！
こ… 恋人？
B-Boyfriend?
なぜ 俺が恋人に…
Why would I be your boyfriend?
好きだからです
なっ…
Because I love you.
岡部さんのことが好きだからです
Because I love you, Okabe-san!
だから 明日一日だけでいいので
So, tomorrow, just for one day...
僕と恋人になってください
Won't you be my boyfriend?
い… いや しかし
N-No, but... You're a gu—
お前は おと…
うっ ううっ…
うっ… 分かった
分かったから泣くな！
Fine...
I'll do it. Don't cry!
いいだろう 明日一日でいいなら
恋人になってやる
Very well.
I'll be your boyfriend for a day,
if it's really what you want.
はっ… 本当ですか？
Really?
な なぜ泣く？
Why are you crying?
だって 僕 うれしくて…
Because I'm so happy...
おおっ…
今 ちょっとキュンときた
That was actually pretty cute.
それで明日 漆原さんと
デートすることになったのか
So, you'll be going out
with Urushibara-san tomorrow?
はい
Yes.
狂気のマッドサイエンティストが
女子高生とデート…
A mad scientist on a date with a high school girl.
言うな だからこうして恥を忍び
Don't say it...
That's why I'm enduring the mortification
助手風情にデートのしかたを
相談しているのではないか
of asking a mere assistant for dating advice.
助手じゃないって
言ってるでしょ！
I told you I'm not your assistant!
ニャ ニャ～
凶真 誰かとデートするのニャン？
You're going on a date with someone, Kyouma?
お待たせしました
アイスコーヒーになりますニャン
Here you are!
Two iced coffees.
デートの相手は まゆしぃかニャ？
Are you going out with Mayushii?
それとも この子なのかニャ？
Or with her?
いいや こいつは助手だ
うっ… ううっ
No, this is my assistant.
奥義修得の任務のためとはいえ
Even if it helps you obtain
your ultimate technique,
手当たりしだいに いろんな子に
手を出しすぎだニャン フフフ…
you're chasing too many girls.
ほお～ ｢手当たりしだいに
いろんな子に｣…
Too many girls, huh?
なっ… お おい！
Hey! Don't say stuff people will misunderstand,
right before you leave!
誤解を生むようなことだけ
言い残して去るな！
う～ん…
ねえ 岡部って その…
Hey... Would you...
Would you do anything to obtain
your ultimate technique?
奥義修得のためなら
何でもできちゃうの？
はあ～ん？
あっ いや だからその…
I-I mean, would Hououin Kyouma do anything?
設定の中での話よ
Why are you talking about this, too?
なぜお前まで設定の話になる？
意味が分からん
I don't understand.
J-Just curious!
な なんとなくよ！
愛する人がいたとしても
I just wondered if you would do anything,
to obtain your ultimate technique,
奥義修得のためなら
何でもできる設定なのかなって…
even if you already had someone you loved...
特に意味はないんだからな！
There's no real meaning behind it, okay?!
なぜ そこで怒る？
Why are you getting mad?
I'm not mad!
怒ってない！
ていうか そんな設定なんだったら
Anyway, if that's how you're supposed to be,
漆原さんとデートしてあげれば
いいじゃない…
why not go on a date with her?
だから 最初からデートすると
言ってるだろ！
I already told you that I was going to!
オカリ～ン
Okarin...
今の話 僕にも詳しく
聞かせてもらいたいわけだが…
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd fill me in on the details.
デートのことなら
If you want to know where to go on a date,
これまで何十人もの女の子と
チュッチュしてきた僕に
I've kissed dozens of girls.
I'll tell you everything you need to know!
任せるといいよ
ネネちゃん シオリちゃん
ホノカちゃん リンコちゃん…
Nene-chan, Shiori-chan, Honoka-chan, Rinko-chan...
それは 全て
ゲームの中の女子だろう？
All those girls are from games.
俺は現実のデートの話を
しているのだ
I'm talking about a real date.
デートといえば 青山だとか
I've heard you go to Aoyama, or Omotesandou,
表参道だとか 西麻布だとか…
or Nishiazabu...
おしゃれでトレンデーな
Fashionable and trendy...
プレミアムな夜に特別なディナー
A premium night...
A special dinner...
おおおっ… 無理だ
これは別世界だ
It's hopeless.
This is a different world...
None of it exists in reality.
現実には存在しない世界なのだ
そこを否定してどうする
What do you get by denying it?
そもそも
I, Hououin Kyouma, was born
アイザック･ニュートンと同じく
ＩＱ170に生まれついた この俺
with an IQ of 170, just like Isaac Newton.
鳳凰院 凶真
興味があるのは 女よりも研究だ…
I am a mad scientist,
and care more for research than girls—
どう見ても 童貞です
本当にありがとうございました
Definitely a virgin!
Thank you very much.
なっ…
そういうお前はどうなのだ？
So, what about you?
そんな偉そうな口を利けるほど
デート経験豊富なのか？
Do you have enough dating experience
to talk down to me?
なっ…
ほ～れ 見ろ お前だって
See?
You've been so busy with studies and research,
勉強や研究に明け暮れて
そういった経験は０なのだろ？
you've never been on a single date, right?
さみしい青春時代を
送ってきたのだろう
You had a lonely youth, didn't you?
うっさい バージンで悪いか！
Shut up! Is it wrong to be a virgin?!
ぬっ…
えっ？
あっ ああ…
｢初デートで重要なのは
With first dates, the most important thing
相手に与える印象を
いかに良くするかです
is making yourself attractive to your partner.
Regarding clothing,
服装に関しては
ブランド物で決める必要はなく
there's no need to wear expensive brand names,
清潔感のある｣…
but something clean...
そこはＯＫだな
I'm fine there.
白衣ほど清潔なものはない
There's nothing as clean as a lab coat.
Who goes on a date in a lab coat?
白衣でデートはないだろ
｢店選びに関しても同じです
The same applies to your destination.
There's no need to pay for an expensive,
high-end restaurant.
無理をして高級店に入る
必要はありません
ふだんの自分の行きつけの店で
十分です｣
The places you normally go are fine.
Normally go...
｢行きつけ｣… ここはないな
This place is out of the question.
当たり前でしょ
Of course it is.
You can't take her somewhere gloomy like this!
この殺伐とした店内で
どんなデートするつもりよ？
他に行きつけといえば…
メイクイーン？
I suppose, the other places I frequent would be...
May Queen.
はあ？ 初デートでメイドカフェ？
A maid café, for a first date?
｢武器屋本舗｣…
武器を買ってどうする！
The weapons store.
Why are you buying a weapon?
てめえ… デートマニュアルを
音読してるだけの分際で
You're just reading from a dating book!
その上から目線はやめろ！
So stop shooting everything down,
この メリケン処女めが…
誰がメリケン処女だ！
American virgin.
Who's an American virgin?
お前以外に誰がいる？
Who else but you?!
Right, right. And you're a virgin, too.
はいはい 童貞乙
Hey, wouldn't this be a better book to read?
つうか そんな本より
やっぱこっちじゃね？
That's an H-game walkthrough!
それはエロゲの攻略本だろ
いいじゃん！ デートっていえば
エロイベントだろ？
Who cares?!
Ecchi stuff happens on dates.
Like holding hands and stuff... That's ecchi!
手をつなぐとか マジ エロくね？
腕組んで おっぱい
肘に当ててんのよ状態とか
Or when she takes your arms,
and presses her breasts against you...
エロすぎっしょ！
That's ecchi as hell!
And at the end of the date, there's a kiss.
そして デートの終わりには
キスして締めだろ？
ちきしょ～う
Damn it all!
Screw all of you, normals!
リア充のバカ～！
結局
何のプランも立たぬまま 朝か…
So, it's morning and I have no plan...
んっ… ブツブツ言ってないで
とっとと着替える！
Stop complaining and get dressed!
タグちゃんと外して
Take off the tags.
Who ties their necktie like that? I can't believe you.
なに そのネクタイの締め方
信じらんない
まったく
世話が焼けるわね… はい
You're a mess, you know that?
Here you go.
なんだか 首輪を着けられた気分だ
I feel like someone just put a chain around my neck.
はい ハンカチも
Here's a handkerchief, too.
どうやって使うか分かってる？
You know how to use that, right?
"I'm still waiting for you."
今でも あなたのことを
待っていますという合図
それは幸せの黄色いやつ
That's for the yellow one,
the handkerchief of happiness.
Where did you learn these things?
その偏った知識は なんだ
おまけに古い
And that's old, anyway.
お前も知ってるではないか
You knew it.
うっ うう… 悪い？
Sorry.
正解は 女の子が公園のベンチに
座るときに広げる
The right answer is,
"You spread it out, before she sits on a bench."
まあ いいわ…
こっそり後をつけて
Whatever.
I'll tail you and message you advice.
いざってときは メールで
アドバイスしてあげるから
なっ… ついてくるのか？
You're coming with me?
So is Hashida.
橋田も一緒にね
えっ？
Operation Valkyria begins!
オペレーション･ヴァルキュリア
開始よ！
なぜ 北欧神話なのだ？
Why Norse mythology?
It is critical that you not be late.
待ち合わせにおいては 遅刻は厳禁
遅くとも
15分前には着いておくこと
Be fifteen minutes early, minimum.
はっ！ ああっ… ふう
岡部さ～ん！
おおっ…
Okabe-san!
I'm sorry!
すみません
早めに
出たつもりだったんですけど
I thought I'd left early.
Were you waiting long?
お待たせしちゃいましたか？
No... I just got here.
ああ いや…
俺も 今 来たところだ
はあ… 良かった
Oh, good...
あっ…
で… では行くか
Th-Then, want to go?
はい
Yes!
うっ…
はっ…
I've never seen you without a lab coat on.
白衣じゃない岡部さん
初めて見ました
Th-This is a date...
ま まあ デートだからな
はっ！
When you're walking with a girl,
女の子と歩くときは
自分は さりげなく車道側を歩く
you should subtly take the side
with the oncoming cars.
どうかしましたか？
Is something wrong?
ああ いやあ… 何でもない
No... It's nothing.
おおっと 何だ あれは！
What is that?!
That wasn't subtle at all!
ちっとも さりげなくない…
When a bike or car approaches, subtly protect her.
そして 車やバイクとすれ違うとき
さりげなく 女の子をガード
はっ… お～っと！
ガードした？
Did he protect her?
岡部さん？
Okabe-san!
あっ たったった…
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
あっ…
と思ったら転んだだけ？
No, he just tripped...
And then a maid helped him up
and gave him tissues!
しかも そこで
メイドさんに助けられ
ティッシュまでもらって
どうする！
What are you doing?
Miss Makise, you seem upset.
牧瀬氏 なんかイライラしてる？
I-It's nice out today, isn't it?
きょ 今日は いい天気ですね
Yeah.
ああ
だが 少し 雲はあるな
But there are some clouds.
そうですね
Yes...
このケーキ とってもおいしいです
This cake is very good.
うん コーヒーもうまい
The coffee is, too.
なぜだ… なぜ
今まで普通に話せていたのに
Why?
My whole life, I've spoken normally with her.
デートと意識した途端…
But now, the moment we're on a date...
ここ ステキなお店ですね
よく来るんですか？
This is a wonderful restaurant.
Do you come here often?
いや
あっ…
No.
This is bad.
このままではマズい…
重要なのは
会話のキャッチボールだ
A smoothly flowing conversation
is the important thing.
Th-This is actually my first time here.
じ 実は今日が初めてなのだが…
あっ…
投げ返した
He actually answered her question?
Today, August 14th, is Patent Day,
初めてといえば 今日 ８月14日は
to celebrate when the first patent
was issued in Japan.
日本で初めて 専売特許が
公布された 特許記念日だ
What kind of conversation is that?
どこに投げてんのよ！
へえ…
You sure know a lot of things, Okabe-san.
岡部さんって
いろんなこと知ってるんですね
えっ… まあな
I-I guess.
Wanna go home, Miss Makise?
牧瀬氏 もう帰らん？
僕たちは見てるだけで
何の役にも立ってないし
We're just watching. We can't help at all.
No, we witness this to the end.
いえ 最後まで見届けるのよ
Thank you.
ありがとうございました
ふう…
あの…
おっ？
Um...
Is it boring?
やっぱり つまらないでしょうか？
僕なんかとデートしても…
Going on a date with me?
バ バカ 何を言う！
What are you talking about?!
Next up, we'll walk around town.
次は町をブラブラするぞ！
ついてこい
Come with me!
うん？
Ruka-chan?
るかちゃん？
So hot...
あっちい～
うう…
He's just walking the whole way to Ueno and back?
ひたすら歩いて
上野まで往復って！
岡部さん
おっ おっ…
Okabe-san...
初めて会った時のこと
覚えてますか？
Do you remember the first time we met?
Yeah...
ううん？
カメラを持った男の人たちに
絡まれて
You saved me, after some men
with cameras accosted me.
困ってたところを
助けてくれたんですよね
あっ ああ…
Yeah.
あ ありがとうございました
Thank you!
でも すみません
But I'm really sorry.
んっ なぜ謝る？
Why are you apologizing?
Because...
だって 僕は…
I look this way, but I'm a guy!
こんな顔なのに男だから
お前が 男だろうが 女だろうが
Who cares if you're a girl or a guy?
関係ない
はっ！
That doesn't matter at all!
そんなことはどうでもいい
Back then,
あの時
岡部さんが言ってくれた言葉が
the words you said made me so happy.
すごくうれしかったんです
あの言葉があったから
It was those words that made me start to like you.
岡部さんのこと
好きになったんです
うっ…
｢そんなことはどうでもいい｣か
"That doesn't matter at all," huh?
あっ… いや ちょっと待て！
Wait! Aren't those memories
from when you were a guy?
それはルカ子が男だった時の
記憶ではないのか？
えっ… あれ 僕…
僕 何を言ってるんだろう
I... What am I saying?
なんだか混乱して…
I feel kind of strange...
It's just like it was with Feyris.
フェイリスの時と同じだ
前の世界線の記憶が…
She's remembering the last world line.
Thank you for today.
今日は ありがとうございました
I was so happy... So happy...
恋人になってくださって
すごく…
So happy you were my boyfriend for today.
すごく幸せでした
おい…
Hey...
これ
お母さんのポケベルの番号です
This is the number for my mom's pager.
ううっ…
ああ…
｢にく にく やさい やさい
"Meat meat vegetables vegetables
meat meat vegetables vegetables."
にく にく やさい やさい｣
If she sees this, I'm sure Urushibara-san's mom
これを見れば
漆原さんのお母さんも
きっと 前のメッセージは
いたずらだったと思うはず
will assume the last one was a prank.
We're ready!
準備できたわよ
はあ…
What's wrong, Okabe?
どうしたの？ 岡部
トゥットゥルー！
Hey, hey...
あのね あのね～！
まゆしぃ さっき るかちゃんが
Mayushii saw Ruka-chan on a date with someone!
誰かとデートしてるのを
見ちゃったのです！
That was Okarin.
ああ それオカリンだよ
No way.
ええ？ ウソだあ
It definitely wasn't Okarin...
あんなの
絶対 オカリンじゃないよ
He was wearing normal clothes,
だって なんか普通の服着てたし
結構 紳士っぽかったし…
and he looked like a gentleman—
そのとおりだ
うん？
She's right...
It wasn't me.
あんなのは俺じゃない
That wasn't a date with the real me!
あれじゃルカ子は
俺とデートしたとは言えない！
オカリン？
Okarin?
はあ はあ…
The date isn't over...
まだ デートは終わってない
えっ？ あっ でも 岡部さん？
But Okabe-san...
Kyouma!
凶真だ！
我が名を忘れたか ルカ子
Have you forgotten my name, Rukako?
男だとか 女だとか 恋人だとか
Guys, girls, boyfriends...
I was the one who got confused.
混乱していたのは俺の方だった
All that doesn't matter!
そんなことはどうでもいい
I finally realized...
俺はようやく気付いた
I am me. And you are Rukako... My student!
俺は俺であり ルカ子はルカ子
俺の弟子だ
はあっ…
Right!
はい！
So bring me the Dark Blade Samidare!
分かったら
妖刀五月雨を持ってこい
えいっ！
そうだ
That's right!
That's just right!
その調子だ
はい！
Yes!
ええいっ！
いいか ルカ子
Listen, Rukako...
Listen well.
よく聞け そもそも
この妖刀にまつわる伝説は
The legend of this dark blade goes back
義経の時代にさかのぼる
to the age of Yoshitsune.
One night, with a full, blood-red moon,
血の色をした満月の夜
道に迷った一人の…
a traveler was lost on the roads...
Look at him go.
やっちまったな オカリン
Good.
よかった
るかちゃんと仲直りしたんだ
He made up with Ruka-chan.
私たちは もう必要ないみたいね
I guess he doesn't need us anymore.
Please save Mayuri-chan.
まゆりちゃんのこと
助けてあげてください
えっ？
The old PC you're looking for...
岡部さんの探している
古いパソコン
The IBN 5100?
IBN5100か？
確かに 去年のお正月まで
ウチの倉庫にありました
Until last New Year's, it was in our storehouse.
なっ…
でも 僕が壊しちゃったんです
But I broke it...
倉庫の掃除をしていた時に
While I was cleaning the storehouse...
だから 僕のせいなんです！
So it's my fault!
Okabe-san, please...
岡部さん お願いします
Save Mayuri-chan!
まゆりちゃんを
助けてあげてください！
久しぶりに
I was so happy to have
the chance to train with you.
岡部さんと修行ができて
本当によかったです
Ruka—
Go.
ルカ…
もう 行ってください
If you don't, I think I'm going to cry...
じゃないと 僕
泣いちゃいそうで…
こういう時は 例の合言葉ですよね
I should say the words, shouldn't I?
El Psy Congre.
エル･プサイ･コンガリィ
Congroo.
｢コングルゥ｣だ
El Psy...
エル･プサイ…
はっ！
I really don't want to go back...
僕 ホントは戻りたくないです
Because... Because...
だって だって… 男に戻ったら
If I go back,
I'll have to seal away these
feelings I have for you!
岡部さんへのこの気持ち
封印しなくちゃいけないから
I think I won't be able to love you if I'm a guy...
男なのに 岡部さんのこと
好きでいちゃいけないと思うから
ルカ子…
Rukako.
If I go back to being a guy,
男に戻ったら 今日のことも
全部 忘れちゃうんですよね
I'm going to forget all about today.
That we went on a date...
デートしたことも
That the two of us trained...
久しぶりに２人で修行したことも
That I was able to touch you this way.
こうして
岡部さんの体に触れていることも
こんなにつらい気持ちを
味わうんなら
If I had to suffer like this,
女の子になりたいなんて
願うんじゃなかった！
I should have never wished to be a girl!
Even if you go back to being a guy...
お前が男に戻っても
俺にとって ルカ子はルカ子だ
You'll still be Rukako to me.
Nothing will change!
何も変わらない！
That's right...
そうですよね
It doesn't matter if I'm a girl or a guy, does it?
男とか 女とか
そんなことはどうでもいい
ですよね
But just for a little while...
でも 少しでいいから
Please remember me
覚えていてください
when I was a girl...
女の子だった僕のことを…
ああ 忘れない 絶対に
I'll never forget it.
うっ うう…
What's wrong, Okabe-san?
どうしたんですか？ 岡部さん
あっ ああ…
Urushibara Ruka.
漆原るか
声もしぐさも女にしか見えない
The mannerisms and voice of a woman...
No... More feminine than any woman.
いや 女よりも女らしい美少女
なあ ルカ子
Hey, Rukako...
はい
Yes?
Do you like me?
お前は俺のこと好きか？
Wh-What are you saying?
い いきなり何を…
Do you?
好きか？
Um... Well, I respect you!
ええっと その…
尊敬してます！
だが…
But he's a guy.
男だ
Just one message left.
残るメールは あと１つ